Just in case something happens, we won't have
to pay for hospital bills because
we have something called a "
what if" so may
the Lord not allow the bread winner to disappear.  Who will
pay that monthly amortization
?
Videos that will make you wealthy and
death free.   Are
you planning to get your
own protection or life insurance?   Are
there people offering you one and
pressuring you to have one?  Well,
if that's your question and you want
to know, this is the episode for you.  Hello
there.  This is Chinkitan, your
national wealth coach.  It's really an
honor and pleasure to serve you everyday
at 8 p.m.  So if you haven't
subscribed here yet, this is the channel for those who are
developing and those who are getting rich.  So please
subscribe.  Today,
we will talk about the benefits of life insurance.
If you miss my first episode about the
three types of insurance that you should
know before you buy, please just find the link
in my comment section.
Just watch it or in
my description section.  Just watch it.  Okay.
What are the benefits?  Ah, there are those
who say, because before we benefit,
someone said, "I don't need
life insurance."  Again, if you are
not a firm believer of life insurance,
you should not watch this video.  Skip
this.  It's just a waste of your time.  But
if you want to know what
benefits it will bring you, keep
watching.  Number one, you will have what is
called financial security
especially for your beneficiaries.  In
other words, it's protection.
This is protection for dependents.
You will have what we call
peace of mind.  Just in case something
happens to the bread winner, the family
can continue to live the lifestyle or
can support whatever
their life plans are.  I would rather
have something than nothing.
I'll ask you a question.  How many of us
have experienced this from our
elders, grandparents, or parents?  When we
disappeared, were we left with
obligations?  Yes.  That's all I can say
.  Especially hospital bills, are
you paying them?  Of course, it would be better
if, let's say, just in case something happens,
we wouldn't have to pay for hospital
bills because we have what's called
life insurance. That would be better.
That's the number one advantage.  Number two,
people always complain about the high
cause of living.  But did you know?
Have you ever heard of what
we call the high cost of dying?  Or what about
funeral and burial
expenses?  In reality, when you
lose a loved one and during that
moment your mind is in turmoil, you can't
think clearly.  Sometimes there
are some people who take advantage.  So
you'll be charged a high price for the
week at the fish market, everything you don't know about,
so you have no choice, you just have to pay.
But if you have life insurance or
you have plans, that's nice, it's
covered, you don't have to think about it anymore.
Just thinking about it makes you sad.
That's number two.  Number three, the
beauty is, if we also have
life insurance, you can also use this to
pay off your debt.  When you say debt, it's
not death, it's debt.  Especially this one
, listen to me carefully.  Especially
for our OFW compatriots, the
breadwinners here, whose house is
paid for or if not, their car is
paid for.  My only question is, are
you making money now?  What if?  May
the Lord not allow the
bread winner to be absent.  Who will pay
that monthly amortization?  Especially
if you have to pay for it for 20 years.  Of course,
if you can't afford it anymore, what
happens?  Will be killed.  So what
happened to what you paid before?
That too will disappear.  Did you know there is an
insurance called MDRP?  Mortgage debt
repayment plan.  MDRP is what happens
in MDRP, that means just
in case the bread winner goes,
the balance of the car
and the house is automatically, is that automatic?  How is
that?  If you want to know, talk to
your friendly neighborhood FA.  Hey,
[ __ ] said something about MDRP that will
automatically pay for what I have.
How is that?  Or, just talk to
them.  Okay.  And then the beauty is
, when you have insurance and
protection, it's a potential source for
savings and investment.  Huh?  Really?  Yes.
Because now there are insurances
called VUL 2 in one.
You already have protection, you still have an investment.
As your money earns,
the interest rate is higher compared to the
bank.  And how about that VL,
again, talk to your friendly
neighborhood Spider-Man,
friendly financial advisors.  Number five,
the number five real benefit
of life insurance, this is what is called
having an income replacement
fund.  What is this income replacement fund?
Just in case the bread winner goes,
automatically the family can inherit the
amount of money that they want to
inherit and that they want to live on
for the rest of their lives.  Woo!  Seriously.
What is that?  You know I'm a bread winner
myself so I have already designed a
program for myself just in case
something happens to me and
my family is covered for the rest of their life.
And of course, before we continue, let
's first congratulate Isam, Piken, and
Rel. Thank you very much.
And number six, benefits.  You can pay off
your educational fund of your children.
You have nothing to worry about.  That's why the
best thing to do is use insurance as
leverage.  This is my tip for you.
Let's say your project is up to
college.  How much insurance do you need
to buy?
You should buy term life insurance to cover
the educational fund of your children.
Term life insurance is only
paid annually.  Because the truth is,
your child is already a refugee, you have no
responsibility for that, so you don't
need that insurance anymore.  And
if you want to know why I'm
teaching that, well,
I'll reveal it to you later.  Last but not
least, this is the best part of
why we need
life insurance, because of what we
call business protection, inheritance
protection.  What does that mean?  Especially
if you already have properties.
We have something called inheritance
tax or estate tax.  You are a widow,
you have property, you will transfer it to the name
of your heirs who need
money.  What if you don't have any
cashed money, what will happen to
that?  The government will not transfer it and there
will be a contestability period
.  And within the contestability
period, if you don't pay it,
interest will accrue.  And when
that expires, what can happen to you?   The
government can sheriff the
property.  That will be lost from your child and will be
passed on to them.  The good news
with life insurance is that once you have
protection, it will cover the taxes
that you won't have to think about anymore and you can pass them on
to your loved ones.  Now, have
you learned a lot?  Please just type
what you learned.